<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>award on Leonardo da Silva Sousa</title>
    <link>https://ssousaleo.github.io/tags/award/</link>
    <description>Recent content in award on Leonardo da Silva Sousa</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ssousaleo.github.io/tags/award/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ACM SIGSOFT Distinguished Paper Award</title>
      <link>https://ssousaleo.github.io/post/icse-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssousaleo.github.io/post/icse-award/</guid>
      <description>Award received for an authored ICSE paper regarding a theory on the identification of design problems in the source code. ICSE is the world&amp;rsquo;s main conference in the field of software engineering. In 40 years of ICSE this was the second time that a paper from Brazil receives such distinction.
Paper: Identifying Design Problems in the Source Code: A Grounded Theory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Identifying Design Problems in the Source Code: A Grounded Theory</title>
      <link>https://ssousaleo.github.io/publication/icse-theory/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssousaleo.github.io/publication/icse-theory/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distinguished Paper Award</title>
      <link>https://ssousaleo.github.io/post/sbcars-award/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssousaleo.github.io/post/sbcars-award/</guid>
      <description>Award received for a co-authored SBCARS paper regarding how developers can effectively find design problems when reflecting upon stinky code. The Brazilian Symposium on Software Components, Architectures, and Reuse (SBCARS) is promoted by the Brazilian Computer Society (SBC) and attracts researchers, students, and practitioners interested in a broad range of software engineering topics, including software product lines, component-based development, architectures, and reuse.
Paper: Revealing design problems in stinky code: a mixed-method study.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revealing design problems in stinky code: a mixed-method study</title>
      <link>https://ssousaleo.github.io/publication/sbcars-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ssousaleo.github.io/publication/sbcars-2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>